

Lesya Stulkivska



Junior FrontEnd Developer

Address

Horishni Plavni, Poltava region, Ukraine

Phone

+38097-994-77-86

Email

jamma@i.ua



HTML₅

CSS3/SASS



JAVASCRIPT/ES6



BOOTSTRAP



GIT/GITHUB



Language

English - A2

Professional Summary

Solution-driven, high-motivated Front End Developer ready to become a part of the team and work for a common result. Would like to grow up and pump professional skills on real projects. My goal is to become a Middle Front End Developer in two years.



Work History

2013-07 -Current

Manager

Sewing manufacture, Horishni Plavni, Poltava region

- Ensured new material shipments at different stages of manufacturing to align with procurement expectations.
- Managed production schedules and arranged timely delivery according to orders.
- Arranged for proper storage and inventory of products.
- Implemented stock inventory software.
- Developed an online store on Tilda.

2011-10 -2013-06

Typesetter

Newspaper "TE", Horoshni Plavni, Poltava region

- Prepared visual and textual materials for production.
- Utilized different technologies, including Adobe InDesign, Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop, to ready artwork for offset printing purposes.
- Generated prepress proofs in digital or other formats to approximate appearance of final printed piece.
- Worked collectively with various partners such as designer, editor, journalist and management team to reach deadlines and meet customer expectations.



Education

2006-09 -2011-06

Master of Science | **Computer Technologies of Publishing** Kharkiv National University of Radio Electronics

2020-10 -Current

No Degree | Fullstack Development GolT Online